Please sit in the waiting room over there, Mrs. Iwakura.
Quindi... signorina Iwakura, la prego di attendere lì nella sala d'attesa.
Lain, there's no need to be worried.
Lain, non devi preoccuparti così tanto.
Come, take a seat over here.
Prego, siediti pure lì.
Ah... would you like a juice or something to drink?
Ah... vuoi un po' di succo o qualcos'altro da bere?
If you don't, that's fine as well.
Va bene se non vuoi niente. Non preccuparti.
Let me see...
Vediamo...
I'm thirsty, so I'll probably make some black tea. Would you like to join me, Lain?
Io ho sete, quindi prenderò del tè... Ti dispiacerebbe unirti a me?
It'd be odd if I was the only one with a drink, right?
Perché sembrerebbe ironico se lo bevessi solo io.
Thank you.
Grazie.
What would you like?
Quale vuoi?
I have all kinds of drinks.
Ce ne sono molti tra cui scegliere.
Whatever you're having.
Lo stesso che hai preso tu.
You want tea as well?
Tè Nero?
Wonderful!
Capito.
Give me just a moment...
Solo un attimo...
You can add sugar and milk as well, if you'd like.
Puoi metterci lo zucchero e il latte se vuoi.
Here.
Ecco qua.
Not bad, huh?
Non male, eh?
Earl Gray - it's one of my favorites.
Tè Earl Grey, lo adoro.
Earl Grey?
Earl Grey?
Right.
Sì.
There are many different types of tea, all with different smells and tastes.
Ci sono anche tanti tipi di tè, con odori e gusti diversi.
Is it good?
Ha un buon sapore?
Well...
Beh...
I think it's very good,
Si adatta al mio gusto.
but I don't know what your taste is like.
Ma non sono sicura che piaccia anche a te, Lain.
Drink a little bit and see if you like it.
Se vuoi, puoi berne un po'.
If it doesn't taste good, we can always make you something else, right?
Se non è di tuo gusto, posso prenderti qualcos'altro.
Here you go.
Ecco...